I'm scared.
Aaahhh!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This ain't a key or something, is it?
Ito Lilia's Pokemon the whole way
Yay
Yes, I mean...
It's been about 6 months, or rather
It's been a long time since I've seen you all!
Gentlemen.
I haven't been able to get my hands on Pokemon cards lately.
This time, I have a lot of them here.
Playburst and Snow Hazard
This is this time, isn't it?
I'm going to do a radio show on CBC Radio called "NiziU46 Ito Lilia no Chattering Time".
I'm doing a radio show called "NiziU46 Ito Lilia no Chattering Time" on CBC Radio.
I'm doing a radio show on CBC Radio called "NiziU46 Lilia Ito's Chatting Time".
The staff of NiziU46 Ito Lilia was so kind as to
They gave it to me as a gift.
They gave it to me as a present!
Thanks a lot!
I try my best every time.
I get up very early and try my best, but
But I can't buy it at all... I have to wait in line
Sometimes they sell out about a meter away from me.
I've been able to buy them without having anything in my hands recently.
I couldn't get these two packs this time either.
I couldn't open them.
But now that I was able to get them, I'd like to open them.
I'd like to open them now.
Now, you opened it.
Okay, first of all...
I'd like to open the clay burst first.
Here it is.
For one box, I guess.
There are two boxes.
It is said that there is one Pokemon card per box.
It is said that there is one Pokemon card in one box.
There is usually more than 1 rare card in a box.
Sometimes there is one card in a box.
So, at least 2 cards are in this box.
At least one of them should contain at least one card.
First of all
Saya Koma
for makenka
Karubou
Nagesutsukasa
Makuta.
I knew it this time.
It's called "What the hell?
There's a Pokemon game called Skyroutt Violet.
There's a girl who's a gym leader.
Her name is Nanjamochan.
She's very popular.
She's cute.
So I have a card of her in my collection.
She's very popular and very rare.
She's extremely popular and extremely rare.
I'm just hoping I'll win.
I don't want that much anymore, to be honest.
To be honest, I don't.
So...
Oh!
HOLETOS EX
TerraStar is here.
Nanjamochan!
So cute!
Here comes the normal Nanjamochan!
Not only is she cute, but she also has great performance.
She's so useful!
And then there's...
Pikachu is cute!
Look at Pikachu!
I look like Pikachu today.
No one is like that.
It's just a coincidence.
The art rarities are so cute these days.
Every picture has a Pikachu
There's a Pokemon called "Ikkanezumi
It's so cute, isn't it?
I want it so much!
And there's Raichu.
I like Raichu so much
You know why?
When I was in kindergarten
I used to play Pokemon.
And...
I usually chose
I usually chose Raichu or Zoroa.
I don't know why.
I chose to play Raichu.
My family has been teasing me about it forever.
They keep asking me to play Raichu.
I don't know...
I got attached to it.
Raichu
Cute little mouse!
Oh! Here it comes!
What the heck?
Seriously, I don't care how many of them there are.
I want a lot of them!I want you to get out a lot.
But... if possible...
I want a special art rare Nujamo!
Nugidama is nice.
Oh!
Dingle EX
I'll open more and more!
So many Pikachus are coming!
At the entrance.
Oh! Raichu! So cute!
I want a Raichu art rare.
No, thanks.
There are many Pokemon in musk violet
There are a lot of Pokemon
If you don't know only old generation Pokemon
you may find a lot of Pokémon that you don't know.
I hope that you will get to know new Pokémon as well.
I don't know so much about Pokémon
Maybe you don't know much about Pokemon
Maybe you are familiar with old Pokemon
Oh!
Nakanu-chan!
Cute!
It's Art Rare!
Art Rare!
She's so cute!
Artlea is really cute, isn't she?
I don't know...
Illustration is too good!
The design is too good!
Cute!
There should be about 3 art rares in a box
There should be about 3 art rares in a box, so there is still a chance
still have a chance!
I still have a chance to get a Raichu.
Raichu, come here!
What's with all the raichu?
This is a little...
I think it's a flag.
Nakanu-chan.
Wandering around
Occasional glimpses
Older
Ah! Sawaro-san!
What?
I've never been here before except for Nanjamochan.
What's with all the new Pokemon and stuff?
I guess it's something like...
It's more like my generation.
I used to play when I was a kid.
I'm attached to Pokemon that appear in games
I'm attached to the Pokemon that appeared in games
After all, I'm all about Taviper and the like.
I was like that a lot.
And the new Pokemon.
They're cute, but...
Personally, I like Atara-Pamo and Pamo-Pamo.
I really like Pamo.
Ah! BACHI-UNI
It's kinda cute.
Isn't it too cute? This snowflake afelie.
I just saw it.
This one...
Nakamura Reno, who's also a member
won it in a "Gacha Gacha" game.
She gave it to me as a present.
With this...
She said, "I'm sure you'll get a good one.
With the help of Reno's power...
What? Why did you bring it? Why?
It's already flagged.
He's already said he'll be here.
Nanjamo said he's coming.
He said he's coming.
Are you guys using various decks right now?
I wonder what kind of decks you're using.
Before, it seemed like Lugia and the like were really strong.
Lugia and the like used to be really strong.
But lately...
I've heard that many decks
I've heard that all kinds of decks are strong all over the place.
Oh! Dinne EX
I saw that earlier, too.
I'm sure there are a lot of people using various decks
I'm sure there are a lot of people using various decks.
But I think I'm more interested in Mew.
or Sir Knight, or...
Super-type Pokémon.
I want to fight.
Oh!
It's a Vanguilas Art Rare!
It's so cool!
What's this?
I got it!
Isn't it really cool? It looks like Godzilla!
It looks like Godzilla!
It's a movie pamphlet!
This is the main Pokemon.
The main Pokemon.I really like the fact that there are Pokemon behind this and other art rares.
I like it very much that there are Pokemon behind this and that.
This one has a Mukabird.
I really like ArtRare!
I'm looking forward to seeing more!
Oh! What!
Second one!
Horetos EX Terrestal.
So you want me to make a self-destruct deck?
This is...
I guess I should make a one-handed deck.
Yes, yes, yes.
What? What is it?
How many? You.
Five.
You want me to put them in the deck?
Can I put them in? Nanjamochan.
I'm sorry to replay this, but...
I'm sorry, but after all this time, SR and SAR still haven't shown up.
Please don't do this.
Please, please, please, come on!
I'll keep coming!
Oh! Oh!
Kanu-chan's art rare!
Kanu and Nakano...
Oh! So cute!
They've evolved!
I really don't know what's going on, but I think it's going to be okay.
Rare frame
Oh! It's a retekirin!
I've always wanted one of these.
Oh, wow! I'm so happy!
Oh, no, no, no, no! Oh, no!
I didn't know that a rare frame would come
Coming in at the end of the day?
Oh! Oh!
Ayako Hino man! Art Rare!
Isn't this look great?
I don't know what to call this.
I mean, it's just like the Vangiras one.
It's like it blends in with the everyday scenery.
It's so realistic!
The background...
I love the fact that there is a Pokemon there.
It's so cute!
What! This is the 6th picture of Nanjamo.
What? Is that possible?
You can have as many as you want.
I can still put it in the deck at this time.
Yes, to put it in the deck.
Oh! Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, yeah?
Mr. Sarlo! I thought you were calling for me. Mr. Sarlo!
I thought it was Nanchamo, but it was Mr. Sarlo.
But it's true, I got a lot of Nanchamo overs.
I'm getting a little scared.
Ah! Lentora! I love Lentora so much!
I'm a big fan of Diamond Pearl.
Well, I actually started with Platinum.
I'm from that generation.
I used to use those models so much that I ended up using the new ones.
After all, when I had Arceus and Scarbai...
Ah! Aaaaah!
Haaah!
Uh-huh.
Oh, this is...
Huh!
I can't touch it for a second.
Oh no!
What is this?
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit!
Why is this happening?
I'm on the verge of tears.
Oh! I'm so happy!
I didn't think I'd cry.
I'm so surprised, I'm in shock, I'm crying.
I've already accomplished what I set out to do.
No, not yet.
I'm still after Raichu and the family mouse.
No, maybe in this world.
We'll get a box full of them.
Maybe there are people who say, "I've got two boxes of these.
But I couldn't buy it.
And when I opened it and found Nanjamochan...
It's a miracle, really!
Well, there is a possibility of getting 2 boxes.
There's a possibility that up to 4 cards will appear.
Still no progress!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What?
Ultraman Ryok.
Are you okay? You're not going to be very unhappy tomorrow, are you?
Uh-oh.
Maybe they sent us a hell of a box.
Uh, I mean, it's outrageous.
Wow.
It's the God round.
Please put "god round" on the thumbnail.
This is too much!Too bad.
So that means you pulled two boxes.
Wow.
What do we do now? What if I get another one, and then I get two boxes?
If I had opened one box...
That's it.
I'm gonna smash my pinky finger on the corner tomorrow.
I'll smash my pinky finger on the corner.
No, but I'm still waiting for Art Rare.
Oh! Here it comes! It's a Heracross!
It's so cute!
It's like summer vacation with a Heracross!
I'm so happy!
But there are 6 art rares, and I think I already got one, so...
I've been waiting for a while...
I'm looking forward to it!
I'd love to hear what you guys are doing with your decks.
If you have any comments on how you use this kind of deck, or if it was fun to make this kind of deck...
If you have any comments, please leave a comment.
Well, there aren't many people around me who do that.
So I have to go to youtube to gather information.
Wow!
I pulled a SAR!
Oh, scary, scary!
I'm sure I'll bump into my make-up ads tomorrow!
I can't believe it!
Oh, this isn't a surprise, is it?
Wait!
What?
It's not a surprise that I'm going to open two boxes of two cards, is it?
It's an EX.
Instoria Art Rare.
This is...
Please write "Gods and Goddesses" on the tamnets.
Ew!
I knew it, I've been trying so hard
I woke up really early, but
But in the end I couldn't buy it.
I think it's all the effort I put into it.
Here.
Heh heh heh heh.
This is bad.
I think it's bad.
Ah!
What? Art Rare is still here.
Hmm? Wait a minute.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
What? Did they come? But...
I don't understand.
The seventh art rare came.
What?
Does that mean there is a possibility that the next one will come? Not yet.
I'm so tired.
I don't know why.
I'm expending a lot of energy.
All of it.
Second elacross.
What's that? What is it?
What's going on?
I mean, we've been here all day.
What? We've been here all day.
What? How many?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine.
That's three boxes open.
Could it be? - No.
I don't understand.
It's a big mess.
Drilleria, we're in a big mess.
Yes, sir.
So, I've finished opening the playburst, and here is the result!
Ta-da-da-da-da! As for the rare ones, there's Mr. Sawaro...
And Nanjamochan, who's already very popular.
DUNYX's Special Art Rare, and DUNYX's Ultra Rare.
It's outrageous!
Ping-pong, ping-pong, ping-pong!
I have an announcement and an apology.
I know I said earlier that it was for the bottom box, but it was three boxes.
I thought that's impossible... but I counted it... and it's 3 times 30.
I counted and found 3 boxes of 30 packs, which means 3 boxes of 30 packs.
I also got an Ultra Rare card, so it's just a matter of time before I get it.
But this time, I honestly wanted to buy this Snow Hazard card.
There is a character named Grusha in this Snow Hazard card.
Grusha is my favorite Scarbai character.
And there are other characters like Art Rare Marilu and Corlippo, so I really want to get them.
I hope I can pull it off.
Ta-da!
Oh, Yadonder is so cute!
Oh, Usokey!
I'm sure there's an Art Rare for Usokey too.
Nokochii!
Wow!
Oh, my God, really!
Wait a minute.
Eh, scary, scary, scary, scary!
Groucho's special art
Oh, I'm scared.
Groucho's Special Art.It's Groucho's special art.
What? Is the radio guy trying to surprise me?
What? I don't get it.
Oh, my God!
Look at this!
Are you okay? Are you sure you're ready for tomorrow?
Oh, my God!
But I'm going to open it.
Not yet... not yet...
It's not a Gods Club anymore.
It's turned out to be a Gods of Gods of Gods of Gods of Gods of Gods of Gods of Gods of Gods.
After all, in today's world...
You can't buy Pokemon cards these days.
Ah! Nokocotchi art rare!
So cute!
We're the same! Today's color
I'm shooting alone this time.
My voice is getting a little raspy.
Too much yelling.
I really think it's just that...
There is such a thing as a greed sensor in this world.
It's like an urban legend manual.
I want something, I want something, I want something...
When you expect something to come, it doesn't come.
If you don't expect anything, the opposite happens.
That's why you're all here in the summer.
We're going on a national tour.
Some of you may have applied for tickets.
If you think you'll win, you'll probably win more than if you think you'll win.
I don't know.
Oh! Here it comes!
The Olin Poe Art Trier!
I've always wanted one of these!
Look at this! Isn't he cute?
You know, he's got his head in the fridge.
And he's looking at it.
It's so cute!
Oh, my God!
I'm sure they're saying it's nothing.
Maybe in the comments section.
Oh!
I didn't know it was that easy.
Surprise!
Peña's SR came out!
Seriously, I've been pulling trainers all the time!
Five items?
That's great! I'm so happy!
Thank you, Ms. Peña!
Oh, I'm only getting another one from here.
Oh, Mimickey!
Mimikyu.
He's right here.
Mimikyu and...
Master Ball.
Come on, come on, there's something here.
Oh, there it is.
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Here it comes!
One-ring love egg!
Yes! I've been waiting for you!
I've been waiting for you!
How do you like that?
Oh! Oh! Here it comes!
Pohjon-EX! They say it's very strong.
I wonder if anyone is using it.
I heard it's strong.
Water's strong, isn't it?
Oh! Here we go! Here comes the AR!
Abrar.
Cute! You know, there are so many tiny Pokémon in Atrea and other places.
I love it. I love it.
Aren't they cute?
Come on, come on! It's Gochimir!
Here comes Atreya.
I do a lot of gawking,
They are waiting for the video. I'm waiting for your video, but I can't do it without your card,
But, after all, we can't do it without a card!
Yes, I have no card, so I can't do it even if I wanted to, and I feel very frustrated, so I hope I can get the next one.
Well, I didn't get the card this time either.
It was pretty much a climax at the beginning. To be honest.
I really don't know what you mean.
I'll tell you, it's a special heart rare of Paojan X.
What?
That's scary!
I don't believe about 60% of what you're saying.
You don't know what I mean!
Special Heart Rare is nothing.
And it's very rare and very strong.
Really?
I was so shocked that I couldn't speak.
I don't know.
How is that possible?
Oh no. Maybe I'll buy a lottery ticket today.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's not good.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh! That's the second kohlippo!
Ah~ so cute~ I'm so happy!Oh, it's so cute, I'm so happy.
I'm so happy, but only one more heart rare?
I'm running low!
Hahahahahaha.
Kittaaaaaaa!
Marilu!
I've been waiting for it, Marilu!
I thought it would never happen because I already have one more Heart Rare.
Marilu came!
I'm so happy!
Now, the last pack. Ta-da!
Oh, a fishing rod.
Yes, so I opened all the snow hazards.
I also opened the third box.
High school 4...
Wow...
No, I really didn't think Grusha would come.
Because as soon as I pulled out the Nanchamocha...
I thought, "Oh, no, Grusha will never come to me.
I thought, "I like her that much," but she came at all.
And it was a special art rare.
And the art rares, too, you know, the ones you're looking for.
Marilu and two ice-poppers came, so I'm satisfied.
I am satisfied. I am very satisfied.
So, here are the rare cards I won this time.
It's a little too overwhelming, isn't it?
Nanchamo came.
Grusha came, and I got both Special Art Rare cards.
Even Ultraman came.
Wow...I'm too excited.
I'm so happy. I'm really happy.
I feel like God saw me the way he did because I couldn't buy it.
I'll keep it in a safe place. I'll never give it to anyone.
I won't give it to anyone. No one.
So, everyone, please watch the next episode if you want to.
Oh, and let me know what you've been up to.
So please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.